

kalpanaravi09.r@gmail.com



No. 47, Thirumurugan Street, Kalaivanar Nagar, Padi, Chennai-600 050.



SUMMARY

Energetic and performance-driven customer service representative with 5yrs of experience improving customer satisfaction and successfully defusing the toughest clients, I love to learn such new things to apply them and doing innovative things efficiently is what makes me happy, and I strive for that.

EDUCATION

Sri Sankara Arts & Science College Bachelor's Degree in Computer Applications 2012 – 2015.

University of Madras

Master of Science in Information Technology 2017–2019 (Distance Education).

SKILLS

- Strong organizational management skills.
- Exceptional communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and as part of a team.
- Detail-oriented and able to handle multiple tasks simultaneously.
- Experience in managing budgets and handling financial documents.

TECHNICAL EXPERTISE

- · HTML and CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- JavaScript
- · React JS
- Basic Concepts of Java
- · Microsoft Office
- · Operating System- Windows

LANGUAGE

- English
- Tamil
- · Telugu

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sales and Management Team

M/S. Airvision Tours and Travels Pvt Ltd Years 2023-2024

- 1. Tour Packages:
- Handles both International and Domestic Packages successfully planned and booked travel arrangements for customers.
- Developed and maintain strong relationship with airline, Accommodation and transportation.
- Demonstrated excellent customer service and problem solving providing detailed planning services to clients, including flights, hotels and transportation
- Assisted customers with passport, visa applications and other travel documents.
- Maintained knowledge of current laws and regulations.

M/S. TakeOff World Tours and Travels Pvt Ltd Years 2015-2019

- 1. Visa:
- Collecting documents from the guest side and verifying the set of documents and schedule the appointment for the types of visas categories from the related embassy.
- 2. Passport:
- Make appointment for Tatkal and Normal passports.
- Explain Procedure for Lost and Damaged Passports.
- · Ecr Clearance.
- 3. **Pcc**:
- Make appointment for police clearance certificate.

DECLARATION:

The information presented in this resume is true and accurate to the best of my knowledge. I assure you that my experience, skills, and qualifications meet the requirements of the job and I am committed to making a positive contribution to your organization.